<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="beg_all_cross">
        <item>
            <sup>393</sup>I beg you, Father, for all the cross and suffering\n
            that you hold ready for me.
            \n\n
            <sup>394</sup>Free me from all inordinate self-will\n
            so that I can fulfill your slightest wishes.\n
            Make me like my Bridegroom;\n
            only then will I be happy and abundantly blessed.
            \n\n
            <sup>395</sup>There is nothing you may never send me—\n
            do everything to break my self-centeredness\n
            so that Christ alone may live and work in me\n
            and in him I bring you only joy.
            \n\n
            <sup>396</sup>Father, you will never send me cross or suffering\n
            without generously giving me the strength I need to bear it.\n
            The Bridegroom in me helps me carry everything\n
            and the Mother keeps watch, so we are always three.
            \n\n
            <sup>397</sup>But if you want to preserve me from suffering—\n
            I only want to comply with your fatherly wish—\n
            then I pray: Keep all misfortune far from me;\n
            you are alone for me life’s guiding star.
            \n\n
            <sup>398</sup>Until now I myself have been at the helm,\n
            too often forgetting you in the ship of my life.\n
            I only turned to you helplessly now and then\n
            to make sure my little ship would proceed according to my plan.
            \n\n
            <sup>399</sup>Father, let me finally be entirely converted!\n
            In my Bridegroom I want to proclaim to all the world\n
            that the Father has the tiller in his hands\n
            even when I do not know the goal nor know the way.
            \n\n
            <sup>400</sup>I now let you lead me blindly;\n
            I only want to choose your holy will.\n
            I will go with you through darkness and night\n
            because your love always keeps watch over me.\n\n
            Amen.\n\n
            
            <b>Reflection</b>\n
            <sup>401</sup>Those who through the Inscriptio\n
            liberate their free will from the strong sheathes of self-centeredness\n
            stand above all things of this world\n
            and are always victorious on the battlefield.
            \n\n
            <sup>402</sup>They joyfully sing with the bride in the Song of Songs\n
            whose life is happily spent in the forges of love:\n
            “Whenever my beloved speaks,\n
            my soul melts like wax before the fire.”
            \n\n
            <sup>403</sup>She no longer knows self-willed forms;\n
            she lets herself be governed by the Beloved in even the smallest things,\n
            just as soft wax takes on the form\n
            the wise molder gives it.
            \n\n
            <sup>404</sup>The molder is the God of eternal love:\n
            the shepherd who anxiously searches out\n
            the lost lamb in the desert brush\n
            until he can count it again in the flock;
            \n\n
            <sup>405</sup>the mother who can never forget the child she bore,\n
            not even in storm-filled times;\n
            the hen that shields her chicks with her wings\n
            whenever the foe frightens them with his threats;
            \n\n
            <sup>406</sup>the king who lovingly and wisely\n
            shelters us with his mighty shield\n
            even on the most dreadful battlefield,\n
            so that not even a tiny cloud can disturb our peace;
            \n\n
            <sup>407</sup>the eagle that carries its small and weak chicks\n
            to the sun on its strong back;\n
            the father who prepares for the prodigal son\n
            a banquet at the throne of sonship.
            \n\n
            <sup>408</sup>At his wish, the bride abandons\n
            and vehemently hates as her enemy,\n
            whatever disturbs the union of love,\n
            even if it is her own flesh and blood.
            \n\n
            <sup>409</sup>“Those who come to me and do not hate father, mother,\n
            wife and children, sister and brother,\n
            those who refuse to consecrate their lives to me\n
            can never be my true disciples.
            \n\n
            <sup>410</sup>“Those who are unable to bear their heavy cross gratefully\n
            can never dare to say\n
            they are truly my loyal disciples;\n
            they have no right to call themselves Christians.”
            \n\n
            <sup>411</sup>Our Lord, who gave up everything for us,\n
            is not satisfied with a life half-given.\n
            He wants our hearts and thoughts completely\n
            and not the pallid glimmer of half-hearted sacrifice.
            \n\n
            <sup>412</sup>Nothing may be allowed to shamefully separate us from him.\n
            If he so wishes, we must deny our own flesh and blood,\n
            detaching ourselves when and as he pleases,\n
            even when our feelings rise in revolt.
            \n\n
            <sup>413</sup>The goal is to win the treasure in the field,\n
            the God of love at the pinnacle of life.\n
            To him all we have and are\n
            is like dust that quickly slips through our fingers.
            \n\n
            <sup>414</sup>He is the pearl beyond all price—\n
            all other glories disappear before him.\n
            Those who have recognized and found him\n
            will joyfully give up everything for him.
            \n\n
            <sup>415</sup>Those who for his sake offer their lives entirely\n
            will experience life’s true happiness and blessing.\n
            Those who hold something back for themselves\n
            will find themselves badly served in every way.
            \n\n
            <sup>416</sup>The God who wants to give all for all\n
            urgently desires of me a life of Inscriptio.\n
            I need not fear the powers of this world—\n
            my being and purpose are to please him.
            \n\n
            <sup>417</sup>In every circumstance I freely give him\n
            my Blank Check, my source of happiness.\n
            The light of faith tells me that whatever\n
            he wishes, permits and ordains is good for me.
            \n\n
            <sup>418</sup>I have experienced this countless times\n
            in all the long years of my life\n
            as long as, in childlike spirit, I let him do as he pleases,\n
            even when the storm raged about my head.
            \n\n
            <sup>419</sup>Those who, like the Bridegroom, are entirely rooted in the Father\n
            and whose lives proclaim the Inscriptio,\n
            will always radiate deep serenity,\n
            even when the tempest rages on all sides.
            \n\n
            <sup>420</sup>They are like a lofty mountain\n
            whose foot is engulfed by stormwinds\n
            but whose peak shines in everlasting tranquility\n
            and never ceases to radiate blessed peace.
            \n\n
            <sup>421</sup>Their faith sees God behind all things,\n
            their ears are alert for the sound of the Father’s voice,\n
            their childlike hearts are always ready\n
            to joyously deliver themselves up to him.
            \n\n
            <sup>422</sup>Even when the Father has permitted suffering,\n
            the child knows how to embrace it in love\n
            and kisses the hand that guides all things\n
            and constantly turns to the Father in prayer.
            \n\n
            <sup>423</sup>Unlike the dog that snaps in rage\n
            at the stone which suddenly disturbs its rest,\n
            the child sees behind each stone the Father’s hand\n
            which kindly invites us to enter our homeland.
            \n\n
            <sup>424</sup>Job, too, in his suffering had to conclude:\n
            “The Lord has given and the Lord has taken away,”\n
            not: “The Lord has given\n
            and the devil has taken away God’s gift.”

        </item>
    </string-array>
    
</resources>