<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="prayer_international">
        <item>
             <small><sup>542 </sup></small>Years ago you set for us the goal\n
            inspired by the Holy Spirit:\n
            to proclaim you, who bear all life in your arms,\n
            the Queen of the World.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>543 </sup></small>We were only a small group then,\n
            but with each passing year and to your glory\n
            we expanded to other noble nations\n
            who live close together with us here.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>544 </sup></small>In your motherly kindness\n
            forgive the failings of our omissions:\n
            that we did not become greater or deeper\n
            or more widely open Schoenstatt’s portals.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>545 </sup></small>Because of this, the world2 is not yet sufficiently mature\n
            to banish the onerous curse of Adam’s sin\n
            or to raise you willingly to the throne\n
            and place the scepter in your hands.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>546 </sup></small>On their behalf accept our humble veneration\n
            and look on our readiness to go to battle.\n
            We present to you the nations living here\n
            who share with us the fate of exile.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>547 </sup></small>Be their Mother and their Queen!\n
            May they return home transformed—\n
            a firm guarantee for peace among the nations\n
            and for unity in the City of God on earth.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>548 </sup></small>Through our striving we want to replace\n
            the love and faithfulness they deny you\n
            through their flight from the cross of Christ.\n
            We want to live for you and your work alone.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>549 </sup></small>Rule over us as pleases God\n
            and make us the salt and leaven of the world.\n
            Let us become one heart and one soul\n
            as Our Lord implored during his earthly life
            \n\n
             <small><sup>550 </sup></small>and despite each individual way remain united,\n
            dedicating ourselves to the Father as an ideal kingdom\n
            and overcoming all barriers of nationality\n
            even when hate infests the masses of the nations.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>551 </sup></small>Increase the numbers and depth of our family\n
            and use us as your instrument forever.\n
            May we fulfill the great mission which you have implored for us\n
            in accordance with the Father’s will.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>