<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
        <resources>
    <string-array name="in_time_of_need">
        <item>
            <sup>501</sup>Mother, take us caringly beneath your mantle,\n
            that we may always live as citizens of heaven.\n
            Preserve us from hunger, epidemics and fire;\n
            Preserve us who turn to you in time of dire need.
            \n
            <sup>502</sup>Speak to your Son as you once did on earth\n
            when he came to our aid in need and distress—\n
            “Lord, they have no wine and no food”—\n
            then he will certainly hear our prayer.
            \n
            <sup>503</sup>He chose you as the second Eve;\n
            you shall save what the first Eve lost.\n
            Just as she drew us into ruin,\n
            from you stream forth the rays of eternal salvation.
            \n
            <sup>504</sup>It is the Father’s loving plan of wisdom\n
            that the earth constantly endure itself as a vale of tears\n
            until the sun of transfiguration rises over it in splendor\n
            and it mirrors heaven’s blessed harmony.
            \n
            <sup>505</sup>In union with your Son you have been entrusted\n
            with giving us the lost life of grace\n
            and with protecting us from many earthly sorrows—\n
            soothing the pain they cause and transforming them into our salvation.
            \n
            <sup>506</sup>Unfold today the richness of your motherly heart\n
            wherever diabolical forces are powerfully at work.\n
            Reveal the fullest extent of your might and kindness\n
            as the Helpmate of the Lord.
            \n
            <sup>507</sup>Just as your Son healed, stilled hunger\n
            and comforted the sick while here on earth,\n
            go with him quietly through our midst,\n
            giving your blessing and helping us with the arm of your unlimited motherly power.
            \n
            <sup>508</sup>Show yourself to all the world as the Great Sign\n
            which neither Satan’s cunning nor earthly sorrow can endure.\n
            Let the nations find protection and salvation in you\n
            and joyfully proclaim you salvation’s Mediatrix.
            \n
            <sup>509</sup>Our affliction, too, has increased so enormously\n
            that without your help we must succumb.\n
            You alone can save us from perdition—\n
            come and see us gathered around you with our pleas.
            \n
            <sup>510</sup>United with your Son, be the one who rescues us\n
            from the fury of hell and the tempests of our times.\n
            We want to gratefully and eternally praise you in every way we know\n
            as the great Mother of the nations.
            \n
            <sup>511</sup>We want to courageously spread your name\n
            and lead all people to your shrine,\n
            so that, with you, they jubilantly and lovingly worship the Triune God\n
            both here and high in heaven above.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>