<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="look_our_family">
        <item>
            <b>Introduction</b>\n
            <sup>448</sup>St. Francis Xavier was exposed to dangers\n
            which were closely connected with shipwreck.\n
            His life was in utmost peril\n
            and only God could preserve him from death.
            \n\n
            <sup>449</sup>In those critical moments\n
            he sensed with ecstasy how deeply he was united\n
            with his confreres everywhere,\n
            on earth and in heaven.
            \n\n
            <sup>450</sup>He recalled their pure and noble striving,\n
            their meritorious and God-pleasing lives,\n
            and for their sake he ardently prayed to God\n
            that he be rescued from a seaman’s death.
            \n\n
            <sup>451</sup>So supernatural were his thoughts—\n
            so deep and warm his brotherly love!\n
            He was so completely united with his community,\n
            so attached to it as his family.
            \n\n
            <sup>452</sup>Because it prospered in God’s sight\n
            and strove to win God’s favor,\n
            he believed that God would especially protect him\n
            and faithfully use him as an instrument for his kingdom.
            \n\n
            <sup>453</sup>Whenever Satan’s cunning and my own weakness discourage me\n
            and I am oppressed by the bitter torment of my failures,\n
            then I, too, can gratefully turn\n
            to our vast capital of grace
            \n\n
            <sup>454</sup>and have recourse to the merits of the noble, pure and steadfast souls\n
            who daily choose the Lord to be their Bridegroom.\n
            He benevolently turns his gaze towards them\n
            and out of love for them will secure my happiness.\n\n
            
            <b>Prayer</b>\n
            <sup>455</sup>I daily offer them and all their strivings,\n
            their holy and vigorous life of sacrifice and love:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>456</sup>When temptation threatens to overcome me\n
            and Satan and the world do not depart:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>457</sup>When I am threatened by life’s uncertainties\n
            and my enemies scatter bombs and shells:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>458</sup>When persecution constantly pursues me\n
            and every meadow becomes a desert:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>459</sup>And when my life is hanging by a thread\n
            because foes are waiting to trap me on every path:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>460</sup>When others, full of malice and blind hate,\n
            seek to destroy and dismantle my life’s work:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>461</sup>When I am accused of every heresy\n
            and all my supporters flee from me:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>462</sup>When others want to tear the souls from my side\n
            whom I have been permitted to instruct:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>463</sup>When courage and trust fail me\n
            because I face tasks beyond my strength:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>464</sup>When I am unable to prudently advise my own\n
            and cannot shield them from harm to body and soul:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>465</sup>When Satan strikes with fierceness and cunning\n
            to erase God from my life:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>466</sup>When it seems that God is letting Satan win\n
            and everything around me wages war:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>467</sup>When I feel poor and naked before God\n
            and yawning chasms open at my feet:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>468</sup>When life’s last hours toll for me\n
            and my conscience raises bitter accusation:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>469</sup>When I stand before God’s judgment seat\n
            and must fear the severity of judgment:\n
                Father, look with mercy on our family\n
                and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.
            \n\n
            <sup>470</sup>I am so intimately united with my own\n
            that we have always seen ourselves as one.\n
            Their sanctity is my life and inspiration;\n
            I would gladly give my life for them.
            \n\n
            <sup>471</sup>I am so tenderly and loyally united with them\n
            that a voice within me always says:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>472</sup>When I am buffeted by life’s wild storms\n
            and passions wreak havoc in my soul:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>473</sup>When the world wants to allure me with its pleasure\n
            and my heart is exhausted, overwrought and parched:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>474</sup>When I am put off by the striving for the heights\n
            and my enthusiasm loses its vigor:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>475</sup>When I am constantly overlooked\n
            and cannot meet the demands placed upon me:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>476</sup>When a heavy workload weighs upon me\n
            and everything pushes me to hurry and to rush:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>477</sup>When my nerves play tricks on me\n
            and failures cool my zeal:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>478</sup>When all my great plans are frustrated\n
            and the world around me wildly bares its fangs at me:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>479</sup>When I am tired of being loyal in little things,\n
            and am more inclined to cry than to laugh:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>480</sup>When God’s Spirit wants to urge me to the heights\n
            but I would rather lie limply in the corner:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>481</sup>When obedience sorely tests me\n
            and no warm sun shines down on me from above:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>482</sup>When the constraints of poverty weigh me down\n
            and siren songs want to enchant my senses:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>483</sup>When it becomes difficult for me to go the way alone\n
            while seeing others happily married:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>484</sup>When the drive to have children oppresses me\n
            and I feel too constrained by my present form of life:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>485</sup>When I have become worn out by my work\n
            and new questions are waiting at the door:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.
            \n\n
            <sup>486</sup>When I am faced with important decisions\n
            and yet balk at going the ways of sacrifice:\n
                What you are and do affects their lives,\n
                determines their misfortune and increases their happiness.\n\n
            
            <b>Conclusion</b>\n
            <sup>487</sup>We are closely united in Christ Jesus,\n
            deeply united in his holy wounds—\n
            we, his members, and he, the mighty Head:\n
            this is the message which no one can take from us.
            \n\n
            <sup>488</sup>As members of his Body we can merit\n
            and gain a right to grace and glory.\n
            As long as we are his true members\n
            the Father will always look on us with kindness.
            \n\n
            <sup>489</sup>If we resemble Christ in what we are and do,\n
            we may extend our hands to one another;\n
            the sanctity of the one will benefit all the others\n
            through the Savior’s Blood.
            \n\n
            <sup>490</sup>So it is that family love will give us wings,\n
            motivating us to discipline our evil passions\n
            and strive for the heights of sanctity\n
            in sacrificial spirit and simple joy.
            \n\n
            <sup>491</sup>Our own striving for sanctity will then become family love\n
            and help the family joyfully bear all sorrow,\n
            drawing down on it the Father’s joyful gaze\n
            and becoming its sure and permanent staff and shield.
            \n\n
            <sup>492</sup>It has its place in the framework of our apostolate\n
            and helps enkindle our zeal for souls.\n
            It is a bond which can never be broken,\n
            uniting us in the city or on the land.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>