<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="morning_consecration">
         <item>
            <b>Greeting</b>\n
            <sup>3</sup>Father, I may awake with new strength \n
            to rekindle my love.\n
            Let me joyfully greet you\n
            together with all your Schoenstatt.
            \n
            <sup>4</sup>We are united in the shrine\n
            where the flames of our hearts\n
            beat for our Mother Thrice Admirable\n
            who, through us, wants to build your kingdom.
            \n
            <sup>5</sup>We kneel in the Holy Spirit\n
            and sing jubilant hymns to Christ,\n
            who sends us with her as instruments\n
            to change the destiny of nations.\n\n

            <b>Thanksgiving</b>\n
            <sup>6</sup>We give you thanks for all the gifts\n
            which we have received in such abundance:\n
            for choosing Schoenstatt\n
            as the place of Christ’s rebirth
            \n
            <sup>7</sup>and the place where you radiate into the world\n
            the glories of our Mother,\n
            so that streams of love may pour forth\n
            to warm cold hearts.\n\n

            <b>Blank Check</b>\n
            <sup>8</sup>Use us according to your will.\n
            Through Schoenstatt may the wide halls\n
            of the holy Church be filled again\n
            and your praise resound to your throne.
            \n
            <sup>9</sup>You may use us for your work\n
            and send us crosses, suffering and hardship;\n
            whether we meet with failure or success\n
            we want to proclaim your love.\n\n

            <b>Inscriptio</b>\n
            <sup>10</sup>May what you have foreseen for us\n
            be realized in every moment of our lives.\n
            We have but a single longing:\n
            Lead us according to your wise plans.
            \n
            <sup>11</sup>Our ideal shall shine before us\n
            and form our entire lives.\n
            For this you have created us in love (P.I.);\n
            for this we strive with all our strength (P.E.).\n
            <i>(Renewal of personal ideal and particular examination)</i>
            \n
            <sup>12</sup>Let us glow like brands of fire\n
            and joyfully go forth to the nations,\n
            giving witness to redemption\n
            and jubilantly leading all people to the Triune God.\n\n

            <b>Confidence</b>\n
            <sup>13</sup>When we consider our own strength\n
            we lose all hope and confidence.\n
            Mother, we stretch out our hands to you\n
            and ask for your many gifts of love.
            \n
            <sup>14</sup>Even in storms and dangers\n
            you will always remain faithful\n
            to the covenant you have sealed with us\n
            and enriched with countless graces.
            \n
            <sup>15</sup>You will send us vocations\n
            who join us in pledging themselves for your kingdom.\n
            You will give us work and richly bless us\n
            and unite your unlimited power1 to our powerlessness.\n\n

            <b>Morning   Offering</b>\n
            <sup>16</sup>What I bear and endure,\n
            what I say and what I dare,\n
            what I think and what I cherish,\n
            all the merits that I gain,\n
            what I direct and what I conquer,\n
            all my joys and all my sorrows:\n
            what I am and what I have,\n
            I give to you as a gift of love.\n
            Use it so that the holy stream of graces\n
            flowing richly from the shrine\n
            may fill the souls of those\n
            who have given their hearts to Schoenstatt\n
            and gently lead there\n
            all those whom you wish to choose in kindness.\n
            Accept everything that our efforts may be fruitful\n
            which we dedicate to the Trinity.\n\n

            <b>Blessing</b>\n
            <sup>17</sup>May God’s blessing come upon all those\n
            who have consecrated themselves entirely to Schoenstatt\n
            and bring them happiness and salvation\n
            here and in eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>