<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="prayer_of_leaders_titles">
        <item>Introductory Remarks</item>
        <item>Prayer</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prayer_of_leaders_texts">
        <item>
             <small><sup>512 </sup></small>1. This   prayer   considers   the   God-willed   relationship between Pallotti and Schoenstatt and prays for its perfect realization.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>513 </sup></small>2. Our image of the human person is the anti-collectivistic person   or   the   everyday   saint   in   the   distinctive   form characterized by the absence of religious vows.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>514 </sup></small>Our image of community is that of a perfect community built    on   perfect    personalities—both         borne    by   the fundamental power of love.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>515 </sup></small>3. In the long run, Schoenstatt’s future cannot be secured without the donum regiminis et contemplationis [the gift of inspired leadership and contemplation].
            \n\n
             <small><sup>516 </sup></small>4. Because we live in the world and have to adapt to it in many ways, the legitimization and sanctioning of our efforts relies on the canonization of saints. For this reason we pray for the two canonizations.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>517 </sup></small>5. Following Pallotti’s example, this prayer especially emphasizes the love of the most Blessed Trinity and of the mysteries of redemption.
        </item>
        <item>
             <small><sup>518 </sup></small>Mother, implore for our small community\n
            in your faithful, motherly way,\n
            that we may always be the soul of Schoenstatt\n
            and dedicate to it our whole life’s strength.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>519 </sup></small>Let us believe in Schoenstatt and Pallotti\n
            and let no one deprive us of this sign of unity.\n
            Let us form the great image of the human person and community\n
            which fulfills the Father’s will.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>520 </sup></small>May the difficult sacrifices we joyfully make\n
            reach up to you as a living plea\n
            to lavish kindness, faithfulness and power\n
            and keep watch over your favorite creation.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>521 </sup></small>Let the spirit of true freedom blossom there.\n
            Draw to it only those who are chosen.\n
            Grant it the Inscriptio as its lasting legacy,\n
            as the fruit of ardent, burning love of God.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>522 </sup></small>Grant it the qualities of leadership it needs\n
            to stride securely through our times,\n
            and on the hard-fought path of life\n
            give it a generous portion of the grace of contemplation.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>523 </sup></small>Use it as your faithful instrument\n
            wherever the spirit of Satan must strongly be defied.\n
            Transform it into Christ’s loyal guard\n
            which always stands out in apostolic spirit.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>524 </sup></small>May it proclaim love for the Blessed Trinity\n
            and bind its finest laurels to the cross.\n
            Through it, bless the Church with genuine everyday sanctity\n
            in answer to the needs of our times.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>525 </sup></small>May the blessing Pallotti once promised\n
            to his entire work\n
            always come upon the family in fullest measure\n
            and bring long-awaited salvation to the earth.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>526 </sup></small>Raise Pallotti to the honors of the altar,\n
            Thrice Admirable, kind and noble Mother,\n
            now that his life’s work is complete\n
            and tenderly greets you with heartfelt love.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>527 </sup></small>May Joseph Engling soon be canonized, too,\n
            so that all resistance may be overcome\n
            which obstructs our fruitfulness\n
            and prevents others from seeing the Father’s plan in faith.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>528 </sup></small>Help it to spread throughout the world\n
            and go victoriously through all the nations\n
            that soon there be one flock and one shepherd\n
            leading all peoples to the Trinity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>