<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="right_hand_wither">
        <item>
             <small><sup>568 </sup></small>Long have I stood with longing at the holy gates;\n
            today they have been opened wide to me,\n
            today I have been admitted to the family—\n
            a fortune greater than my heart can fathom!\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>569 </sup></small>I can think of nothing more beautiful on earth\n
            than to give myself to our family,\n
            to really be its child in body and soul\n
            and to devote to it all my strength.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>570 </sup></small>Others can sing their communities’ praises\n
            and develop there in their own way,\n
            but for me there can be no greater happiness\n
            than to generously strive according to our ideals.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>571 </sup></small>From now on I may wear the brooch.\n
            It shall rejoicingly tell the whole world\n
            that I have been and will remain accepted\n
            in the family for which I was born.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>572 </sup></small>I live in the family which was created\n
            because God chose me for it in kindness.\n
            There and nowhere else on this earth,\n
            can my salvation be so secure.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>573 </sup></small>The Mother has graciously accepted me\n
            and pledged, as only she can pledge,\n
            to faithfully care for me in all life’s situations,\n
            so that, joyfully, I one day see the Easter morning.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>574 </sup></small>Because I belong completely to our Savior and his Mother,\n
            who constantly bend down to me in kindness,\n
            I can heroically fight for true freedom\n
            and daily offer it to God with joy.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>575 </sup></small>In royal freedom I may travel\n
            from place to place when God so wills it,\n
            but I will never abandon the family\n
            that seeks to embrace me with tender love.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>576 </sup></small>I have received a new father and a new mother\n
            and many sisters of noble stature.\n
            I have the right to carry them in my heart\n
            and to find a home in theirs.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>577 </sup></small>What they love and suffer, pray, intend and do\n
            helps me reach the eternal harbor.\n
            Whatever they acquire through loving sacrifice\n
            will also help me one day joyfully sing hymns of victory.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>578 </sup></small>For the sake of their pure and noble striving\n
            the Father seeks to richly fill my soul\n
            and the Mother looks on me with benevolence\n
            because in Christ they go in simple pilgrimage to the Father.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>579 </sup></small>Their courageous march through the currents of the times\n
            will high-mindedly broaden my heart and mind;\n
            the honors which they have honestly won\n
            will increase my family consciousness.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>580 </sup></small>Their heroic and noble striving for sanctity\n
            will give me new incentive day by day.\n
            With them I want to strive for the palms of victory\n
            and sing joyful psalms of love.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>581 </sup></small>My fate is so interwoven with the family’s\n
            that all who praise it must praise me\n
            and all who despise it must despise me, too—\n
            so much must we be seen as one!\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>582 </sup></small>Whatever the family does which pleases God\n
            and whoever enters as a new child into its ranks\n
            touches me as if it were my very life—\n
            the family is, will ever be, my second self on earth.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>583 </sup></small>The wrinkles that it has, its flaws and weaknesses,\n
            can never destroy my reverence for it.\n
            I will never allow its humanness\n
            to separate me from my great love for it.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>584 </sup></small>I will always refuse to proclaim abroad\n
            the things which cannot increase the family’s honor.\n
            Over such things I will cast the veil of silence\n
            and atone for them by living my life in holiness.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>585 </sup></small>I will never leave my family’s side\n
            even when it disappoints me.\n
            I want to repay it for everything it has given me\n
            and always urge its efforts to the highest heights.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>586 </sup></small>We will remain unshakably united.\n
            May the flames of family love burn brightly.\n
            With it we want to go into battle and win the day;\n
            it is through us that the family must fulfill its mission.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>587 </sup></small>We who once stood at the altar\n
            will never be the cause of the family’s shame.\n
            The loyalty that we swore at the altar\n
            will stand forever, and no one will be lost.\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
            \n\n
             <small><sup>588 </sup></small>I consider it one of the greatest graces I have received\n
            that on the paths of my life\n
            God’s kindness graciously led me to the family—\n
            Oh, that I could give the thanks which that deserves!\n
                O God, may my right hand wither,\n
                should I forget you, Schoenstatt.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>