<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="schoenstatt_office">
        <item>Remarks</item>
        <item>Introduction Prayer</item>
        <item>Matins</item>
        <item>Lauds</item>
        <item>Prime</item>
        <item>Terce</item>
        <item>Sext</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Vespers</item>
        <item>Compline</item>
        <item>Concluding Prayer</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="schoenstatt_office_texts">
        <item>
            We take it for granted that our love’s active dialog with God
            has a Marian character. Whether we practice this by expressly
            living    each   day   with   our   Mother     Thrice    Admirable      of
            Schoenstatt, or are satisfied when our daily life with God takes
            on a Marian hue, is a question of personal development in the
            life of grace. In either case, we must all come to the point,
            sooner or later, when we can say:

            “Let us abide in holy triple unity, and thus go in the Holy Spirit
            to the Father .”\n

            This   little   office   aims   at   promoting   and   securing   such   a
            development.   It   can   be   prayed   before   the   corresponding
            canonical hour as a preparatory prayer, for it adopts the main
            liturgical themes of the Roman Breviary and applies them to
            our original world of values. It can also be used separately as
            an office in its own right.\n

            The structure of the hours is not difficult to discern. The first
            two lines determine the theme and essence of the given hour.
            The   first   verse   considers   the   biblical   place,   the   second
            considers its unique realization in Schoenstatt and the third
            is a prayer relevant to the hour’s theme.\n

            The preparatory prayer should be prayed before each hour.
            When   prayed   in   community,   the   verses   can   be   prayed
            alternately between two choirs [e.g. left and right], with the
            first two lines said by a leader and the third and fourth verses
            recited by all. The concluding prayer [“O Triune God”] is not
            meant to be said after each hour, but only as a conclusion to
            the entire office.\n

            Meditating on the office as a whole, one can easily follow the
            course of the day in the image of the sun and symbolically
            apply it to Christ.\n

            For those who are so inclined, the time between the canonical
            hours (about three chronological hours) can be inspired by
            the chosen image of the sun or by the biblical place. This will
            appeal especially to nature lovers who are already inclined to
            follow   the   course   of   the   sun,   and   whose   symbolic   and
            religious thinking naturally applies this image to Christ. In this
            way, their attention to the course of the sun can be readily
            transformed into a living relationship with Christ. In addition,
            the references to the various biblical places, along with their
            Marian interpretation, can help foster a living relationship
            with Mary. The application of this symbolism to our shrine,
            when properly understood, can help foster a living relation-
            ship with our Mother Thrice Admirable and her shrine.
            If a common time is agreed upon, a spontaneous awareness
            can develop that our everyday lives are also spent in the
            presence of one another and with the [entire Schoenstatt]
            family. That can strengthen the sense of community, a matter
            of no small importance, especially for those working in the
            missions and the diaspora.
        </item>
        <item>
            <small><i>(at the beginning of each hour)</i></small>
            \n
            <sup>179</sup>In Spirit I kneel before your picture,\n
            Thrice Admirable, strong and gentle Mother,\n
            united with all who have consecrated themselves to you\n
            and are ready to die for your realm.
            \n\n
            <sup>180</sup>We want to mirror ourselves in your image\n
            and seal our covenant of love anew.\n
            Make us, your instruments, like you in everything\n
            and through us build Schoenstatt everywhere.
        </item>
        <item>
             <sup>181</sup>Your shrine is our Nazareth,\n
            concealed in the night of our times.
            \n\n
            <sup>182</sup>Immaculate Virgin, you struggle there in prayer,\n
            filled with longing for the dawn of salvation.\n
            There Gabriel speaks God’s request\n
            and your Fiat illumines the world.
            \n\n
            <sup>183</sup>Again I see you quietly speaking your Fiat\n
            and see your light breaking through the night from Schoenstatt,\n
            for God in his wisdom and mercy has chosen it\n
            to be a bright beacon for the world of today.
            \n\n
            <sup>184</sup>Like you, let me always be faithful to the Blank Check\n
            and fight the battle against the ancient dragon.\n
            As your instrument let me always be ready to serve you\n
            and joyfully dedicate my life to Schoenstatt’s mission.
            \n\n
            <sup>185</sup>Glory be joyfully given to the Father\n
            through Christ with Mary, highly praised,\n
            in the Holy Spirit full of splendor\n
            from the universe now and in all eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
            <sup>186</sup>Your shrine is our Bethlehem,\n
            pleasing to God through its sunrise.
            \n\n
            <sup>187</sup>There you gave virginal birth to the Lord\n
            who chose you as his Bride and Mother.\n
            In your miraculous fruitfulness\n
            you brought forth the Sun of Righteousness.
            \n\n
            <sup>188</sup>You have graciously established Schoenstatt\n
            so that our times can see the Eternal Light.\n
            From there you want to go through our dark world\n
            as the Christbearer sent by God.
            \n\n
            <sup>189</sup>Jubilantly place the Lord into my soul anew,\n
            so that, like you, I may perfectly resemble him.\n
            Let me be a Christbearer for our times,\n
            that they may shine in the brightest radiance of the sun.
            \n\n
            <sup>190</sup>Glory be joyfully given to the Father\n
            through Christ with Mary, highly praised,\n
            in the Holy Spirit full of splendor\n
            from the universe now and in all eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
            <sup>191</sup>Your shrine is our Nazareth\n
            where Christ, the Sun, warmly shines.
            \n\n
            <sup>192</sup>This sun, with its clear and radiant light,\n
            forms the history of the Holy Family\n
            and awakens strong and silent everyday sanctity\n
            in blessed family unity.
            \n\n
            <sup>193</sup>Through this Nazareth for homeless times\n
            God wants to prepare salvation for families\n
            and mercifully bestow everyday sanctity\n
            on those who dedicate themselves toSchoenstatt.
            \n\n
            <sup>194</sup>Mother, let Christ shine in us more brightly\n
            and join us together in holy community,\n
            always ready for the sacrifices\n
            our holy mission may demand of us.
            \n\n
            <sup>195</sup>Glory be joyfully given to the Father\n
            through Christ with Mary, highly praised,\n
            in the Holy Spirit full of splendor\n
            from the universe now and in all eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
             <sup>196</sup>Your shrine radiates into our times\n
            the brilliance and splendor of Tabor’s sun.
            \n\n
            <sup>197</sup>Where Christ, the Sun, reveals his glory\n
            and makes known his victory as once he did on Tabor.\n
            It is good to be there, as in Paradise,\n
            because it is the Holy Spirit’s dwelling.
            \n\n
            <sup>198</sup>Entirely enveloped in the brilliance of Tabor’s sun\n
            as the vessel open to the Holy Spirit,\n
            you work in Schoenstatt as Mediatrix\n
            and mercifully lead us to the Holy Spirit.
            \n\n
            <sup>199</sup>Let us be deeply penetrated by Christ’s Spirit\n
            and richly bless us with eloquent tongues of love,\n
            so that Christ’s glory may shine through us\n
            as it does through you, the Mirror of Justice.
            \n\n
            <sup>200</sup>Glory be joyfully given to the Father\n
            through Christ with Mary, highly praised,\n
            in the Holy Spirit full of splendor\n
            from the universe now and in all eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
            <sup>201</sup>The sun is shining at its zenith:\n
            we recollect our hearts in Bethany.
            \n\n
            <sup>202</sup>With eager expectation you took in everything\n
            which came from the mouth and heart of the Lord\n
            and became a master of contemplation,\n
            totally given to God in tender intimacy.
            \n\n
            <sup>203</sup>In your shrine you wish to form\n
            an army of prayer in the midst of a barren world,\n
            leading us to love’s highest heights\n
            so that in the battle we remain loyally at your side.
            \n\n
            <sup>204</sup>Help me to learn more and more the spirit of prayer\n
            and always lift my heart to the stars of heaven.\n
            Let me always look on Christ, the Sun,\n
            and trust in him in all of life’s situations.
            \n\n
            <sup>205</sup>Glory be joyfully given to the Father\n
            through Christ with Mary, highly praised,\n
            in the Holy Spirit full of splendor\n
            from the universe now and in all eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
             <sup>206</sup>The sun silently proceeds on its course of blessing\n
            as the Spirit leads us on to Golgotha.
            \n\n
            <sup>207</sup>There I see your motherly heart powerfully renounce\n
            and courageously annihilate each right as mother.\n
            With your only-begotten Son you offer yourself to the Father on the throne\n
            for the salvation of the world.
            \n\n
            <sup>208</sup>In the shrine you wish to form souls\n
            who are always priestly in their life and bearing,\n
            standing as deacons at the foot of the cross\n
            and going the way of the cross with the Redeemer.
            \n\n
            <sup>209</sup>Through my life of sacrifice let me complete—\n
            in keeping with eternally valid laws and the spirit of the Inscriptio—\n
            whatever fullness is still lacking\n
            in the cross and suffering of Christ.
            \n\n
            <sup>210</sup>Glory be joyfully given to the Father\n
            through Christ with Mary, highly praised,\n
            in the Holy Spirit full of splendor\n
            from the universe now and in all eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
            <sup>211</sup>The sun makes ready for the night\n
            and invites us to enter the Cenacle.
            \n\n
            <sup>212</sup>There you implored the Spirit for the Church\n
            who freed her from the scourge of half-heartedness,\n
            guided her to the teaching of Christ\n
            and enkindled in her the spirit of the apostles and the martyrs.
            \n\n
            <sup>213</sup>That is how you want to work in our shrine:\n
            strengthening our weak eyes of faith\n
            so that we might see life as God sees it\n
            and always walk by heaven’s light.
            \n\n
            <sup>214</sup>In this light of faith let me see\n
            how the Father’s love wished to accompany me today.\n
            Let loyalty to our mission be my thanksgiving\n
            for the boundless gifts he has showered on me in love.
            \n\n
            <sup>215</sup>Glory be joyfully given to the Father\n
            through Christ with Mary, highly praised,\n
            in the Holy Spirit full of splendor\n
            from the universe now and in all eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
            <sup>216</sup>Silent and tired, the sun now goes to rest\n
            and Sion smiles on us from afar.
            \n\n
            <sup>217</sup>Your dying was an ecstacy of purest longing;\n
            your body never knew corruption.\n
            You reign now transfigured in the “Holy City,”\n
            on Sion, which God has opened to you.
            \n\n
            <sup>218</sup>Through the shrine you constantly direct us upwards\n
            to the eternal Schoenstatt where we will one day praise God.\n
            You show us the transitoriness of the earthly world\n
            until you have led us to things eternal.
            \n\n
            <sup>219</sup>Teach me to live each day so that my dying\n
            becomes easy, as befits an heir of heaven.\n
            Teach me to judge myself each night in such a way\n
            that after death I may see you and God.
            \n\n
            <sup>220</sup>Glory be joyfully given to the Father\n
            through Christ with Mary, highly praised,\n
            in the Holy Spirit full of splendor\n
            from the universe now and in all eternity.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
            <sup>221</sup>O Triune God, be eternally praised\n
            for all the great things you have done for us:\n
            for giving Schoenstatt a Mother\n
            and for immersing us, through her, deeply into Christ.
            \n\n
            <sup>222</sup>We praise you because Mary’s life\n
            has given us the norm for our daily living\n
            and brought the splendor of Christ the Sun\n
            so humanly near to us.
            \n\n
            <sup>223</sup>With jubilation we unite all the praise\n
            which burns like flames of love through all creation.\n
            Blessed Trinity, we bring it to you and to your altar\n
            in Jesus and Mary forevermore.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>