<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="shepherds_prayer">
        <item>
            <sup>529</sup>Thrice Admirable Schoenstatt Lady,\n
            look on those whom I entrust to you.\n
            I must watch them stand alone in battle,\n
            can only go my way with trust in you.
            \n\n
            <sup>530</sup>Command the turbulent storms of the times\n
            so that their reckless fury does not increase unchecked.\n
            Bring the devil’s power and cunning to nought\n
            and deliver my own from the curse of Eve’s sin.
            \n\n
            <sup>531</sup>Silence their evil, inordinate drives;\n
            let their entire being bow to God!\n
            To him should belong the glow of their hearts,\n
            to him the loyal dedication of their sacrificial love.
            \n\n
            <sup>532</sup>Help them resolutely withstand each love\n
            which would subtly tear them from your side,\n
            which would dull the brilliance of their purity\n
            and wilt the crown of their virginity.
            \n\n
            <sup>533</sup>They have made a covenant with you.\n
            May it stand as firm as if cast in bronze.\n
            Then I will know that they are in safe and loyal hands\n
            and will not fear the raging fury of the flood.
            \n\n
            <sup>534</sup>You will bring them all victoriously home to the Father\n
            so that they can sing hymns to the Lamb.\n
            I firmly believe that no one will be lost\n
            who remains faithful to the covenant of love.
            \n\n
            <sup>535</sup>Through them you want to bless Schoenstatt\n
            and proclaim to everyone they meet\n
            that you have chosen it as your instrument\n
            and are leading it onwards to the heights of the Inscriptio.
            \n\n
            <sup>536</sup>I therefore inscribe into your heart once more with blood and fire\n
            all those I hold so dear\n
            and proceed without fear along that path in life\n
            which the Father’s wisdom has foreseen for me.
            \n\n
            <sup>537</sup>If he chooses that my life become the ransom,\n
            I joyfully place it at his disposal.\n
            In return, may all who have dedicated themselves to you and Schoenstatt\n
            live with the Blessed Trinity forevermore.\n
            Amen.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>