<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="take_this_child">
        <item>
            <h4>Introduction</h4>
            <sup>425</sup>Ignatius once asked himself in prayer\n
            what would most cause his heart to shudder\n
            if God were suddenly to desire of him\n
            the ultimate and greatest proof of his love.
            \n
            <sup>426</sup>He could quickly answer Eternal Wisdom:\n
            More than life and very self\n
            he loved the Order to which he had dedicated his strength\n
            and for which he would gladly give his life.
            \n
            <sup>427</sup>“If God,” he said, “were to demand it of me,\n
            if he were to let this new flock be destroyed\n
            which I have founded at his wish\n
            and for which I loudly praise his goodness,
            \n
            <sup>428</sup>my heart would struggle restlessly\n
            for a quarter of an hour\n
            after receiving the news of its death…\n
            Then God would be Lord of this disquiet, too.”
            \n
            <sup>429</sup>Is not the small and noble family kingdom,\n
            which strives to resemble the Blessed Trinity,\n
            inscribed deeply into my heart, too,\n
            far more than anything else a person can love?
            \n
            <sup>430</sup>Neither mother nor father\n
            with all their noble parental love\n
            could cherish their dearest child\n
            as deeply as I love this family chosen by God.
            \n
            <sup>431</sup>For its sake I would gladly give up my good name,\n
            life and limb, health, strength and talents\n
            if it would better serve the family’s interests\n
            and gain for it the crown of God’s love and fruitfulness.
            \n
            <sup>432</sup>For its every custom, even the smallest things,\n
            I want to sing a jubilant song of praise and thanks.\n
            I relinquish nothing, absolutely nothing of all these things\n
            and offer my life’s strength and toil for it all.
            
            <h4>Prayer</h4>
            <sup>433</sup>Almighty God, do you want to take this child from me?\n
            Will it please you to paralyze its strength?\n
            Is it meant to be disfigured in your sight,\n
            retaining but a pale glimmer of life?
            \n
            <sup>434</sup>Out of love you gave me this child,\n
            and gave me the strength to dedicate my entire life to it.\n
            Do you want to see it dead in my arms?\n
            Should it go through life a cripple?
            \n
            <sup>435</sup>Then I ask you: Carry out your plans,\n
            for to you alone goes out my deepest longing.\n
            I only seek you, Father, and your will,\n
            am happy when you fulfill your wishes.
            \n
            <sup>436</sup>Accept the child which you endowed with life\n
            and to whom you let me give the entire strength of my love.\n
            I joyfully place it back into your hands,\n
            its future destiny and its happiness in life.
            \n
            <sup>437</sup>But if in the fullness of your mercy\n
            you want to return it to me and the world,\n
            allowing me to further embrace it with my love,\n
            if as a ransom you only want to see my plea, my childlike and heroic trust,
            \n
            <sup>438</sup>then I will hate all half-heartedness and laziness\n
            and never disgracefully cease by either day or night\n
            to pray and beg with unfailing confidence:\n
            Let your child soon see miracles!
            \n
            <sup>439</sup>May its life become a faithful reflection\n
            of our Mother’s life here on earth,\n
            so that through it the splendor of her rays\n
            may be revealed to our ailing times.
            \n
            <sup>440</sup>I will not stop imploring full of trust\n
            that your plans be fulfilled;\n
            you may put my faith and my trust to the test—\n
            I will believe in our mission heroically.
            \n
            <sup>441</sup>And if I myself may not see\n
            the prospering of your child in your presence,\n
            then I, like Moses, will remain on the mountain…\n
            Only grant this child the happiness of the holy land!\n
            Amen.
            
            <h4>Reflection</h4>
            <sup>442</sup>May our Mother implore for us such earnestness;\n
            then we will be able to pass through every storm victoriously.\n
            She will see to it that the Father\n
            will return the child to us in fatherly kindness.
            \n
            <sup>443</sup>But we must first present the child to him without reserve\n
            and completely direct all our love to him alone.\n
            With great love and kindness he will then return the child to us,\n
            even if at the last moment, as he did Isaac.
            \n
            <sup>444</sup>He will make of it a great sign of his promise\n
            and himself become the child’s generous guardian.\n
            He will make it grow and prosper like the sand on the shore\n
            to the glory, praise and honor of the Trinity.
            \n
            <sup>445</sup>He will bless it with many holy children\n
            who loyally proclaim the praises of our Mother.\n
            He will let it become the salt and light of the earth\n
            which strengthens, warms and brightens the Church and world.
            \n
            <sup>446</sup>He will let it stride with courage and holy liberty\n
            through depersonalized and turbulent times,\n
            using it everywhere as a noble herald\n
            of true freedom joyfully dedicated to God.
            \n
            <sup>447</sup>I will gladly bear forever the somber chains of slavery\n
            if it stands as ransom for the family’s freedom…
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>