<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="pk_phrases">
        <item>Let us be deeply penetrated by Christ’s spirit.</item>
        <item>What is sanctity? It is the love of the child for the father.</item>
        <item>What is needed in the Church and the world today is saints… people who firmly take their stand…</item>
        <item>To pray means: bowing one’s head to let the Father’s gentle and strong hand rest on it.</item>
        <item>See it through bravely!</item>
        <item>Our shrine is the cathedral of love for our present time. At its walls the suffering of mankind should be broken. M.p.h.c.</item>
        <item>Take great pains not to disturb God’s plans in the least.</item>
        <item>The things I suffer and I bear… I give to you as a gift of love.</item>
        <item>For all of us, you are the same: Father and rich in love.</item>
        <item>Father, let me finally be entirely converted!</item>
        <item>One heart in the Father.</item>
        <item>Father, purify our souls and make us hearers of your Word.</item>
        <item>Keep me pure in body and soul.</item>
        <item>Each one of us must achieve the highest conceivable degree of perfection and sanctity according to his state of life.</item>
        <item>Blessed are those who hunger and thirst.</item>
        <item>Mother, kindly lead us today.</item>
        <item>Father, look with mercy on our family and for its sake reveal your wondrous love.</item>
        <item>The time spent for love will never cause us regret, it will enrich us for eternity.</item>
        <item>Let me be a sun for all!</item>
        <item>My destiny rests in Father’s hands.</item>
        <item>You will give us work and richly bless us and unite your unlimited power to our powerlessness.</item>
        <item>Do not worry anxiously! The greatest care: to be endlessly carefree.</item>
        <item>Yes, Father!</item>
        <item>Your conversation shall be in heaven – in Father’s heart and will and in his world of values.</item>
        <item>What is sanctity? It is the love of the child for the father.</item>
        <item>Let us remain true to the Blessed Mother!</item>
        <item>Even when the Father has permitted suffering, the child knows how to embrace it in love.</item>
        <item>I see Her as my home, my fortress and my constantly flowing source of joy.</item>
        <item>I love those who love me.</item>
        <item>The hour of your love has come!</item>
        <item>It is in the plan this way! –strive for selflessness and simple inconspicuousness—</item>
        <item>The only reason for sadness is the lack of personal sanctity.</item>
        <item>I and the Father are one! Mphc! </item>
        <item>I, too, place all the bitter suffering of my soul ever at your disposal for the capital of grace.</item>
        <item>Here I am Lord, send me wherever you will!</item>
        <item>Let us glow like brands of fire.</item>
        <item>May the Blessed Mother now begin to be effective from your home shrine as the great teacher. Amen.</item>
        <item>Your hearts have struck fire.</item>
        <item>Make sacrifices for God.</item>
        <item>It is in the plan this way.</item>
        <item>Please study all that has developed through this deep and childlike love for Mary!</item>
        <item>Accept Oh Lord my entire freedom.</item>
        <item>Let me be a living MTA Shrine for the glorification of the Father!</item>
        <item>Nothing can satisfy us like the Eternal, Infinite.</item>
        <item>With joy and in apostolic spirit I offer with you my will as an instrument to Christ.</item>
        <item>Let your child soon see miraculous deeds! Mphc</item>
        <item>Everyday sanctity is possible for each one of us.</item>
        <item>You may always find me in the shadow of the Shrine.</item>
        <item>Let us walk like you through life, let us mirror you forever, strong and noble, meek and mild, peace and love be our endeavor.</item>
        <item>Even in storms and dangers, you will always remain faithful.</item>
        <item>Send Oh Lord laborers into your vineyard.</item>
        <item>I am ready!</item>
        <item>I am the Father’s child.</item>
        <item>The works of God begin from nothing.</item>
        <item>God is Father, God is good, everything he does is good.</item>
        <item>A kind word is a bridge not only to neighbor but also to God.</item>
        <item>Lord, detach me from myself: Then you have won the battle with me. Mors sola.</item>
        <item>We are closely united in Christ Jesus deeply united in His holy wounds.</item>
        <item>The cross solves all of life’s puzzles!</item>
        <item>Gain for yourselves abundant merits… by a zealous life of prayer.</item>
        <item>God is our Father!</item>
        <item>Build an ark.</item>
        <item>Every time we praise Mary, we praise God and Christ.</item>
        <item>During my whole life I have said ‘yes’ to God every moment.</item>
        <item>I know that you are my Father in whose heart I am sheltered!</item>
        <item>Use us according to your will.</item>
        <item>To God our Father let the praises soar, through Christ with Mary blessed for evermore, in God the Spirit, full of majesty, from all the world for all eternity. Amen</item>
        <item>Our ideal shall shine before us and form our entire lives.</item>
        <item>Deeply fill our souls with the love that comes from you.</item>
        <item>The aim of our piety is the blank check surrender, conformity with God’s will.</item>
        <item>The main thing is this and remains – the spirit of the inscriptio.</item>
        <item>You have my plan your own.</item>
        <item>Form us into royal children.</item>
        <item>God alone suffices…</item>
        <item>She will work miracles! </item>
        <item>The smallest children are the heavenly Father’s favorite.</item>
        <item>Our Lord, who gave up everything for us, is not satisfied with a life half-given.</item>
        <item>Sanctity is the simplest thing in the world</item>
        <item>I am wholly convinced that it is possible to base one’s entire life on the covenant of love.</item>
        <item>The Mother Thrice Admirable!</item>
        <item>Mother, inscribe us in your heart and lead us with you heavenwards.</item>
        <item>Mother let me be finally converted.</item>
        <item>Despite the darkness around me, I fall into God’s hands.</item>
        <item>Faith and love must be espoused to heroic love for the cross.</item>
        <item>Mother will take care and be victorious!</item>
        <item>How often in world history have small and insignificant beginnings been the source of great and greatest accomplishments?</item>
        <item>I will go with you through darkness and night, because your love will always guard me.</item>
        <item>Adsum!</item>
        <item>She dwells and works, she acts and transforms, she forms and molds, she changes and she sends.</item>
        <item>M.p.h.c.</item>
        <item>I will draw youthful hearts to myself…</item>
        <item>We will help build the Church at the new shore!</item>
        <item>Nothing is mere coincidence; everything comes from God’ providence.</item>
        <item>I know that we, by building on what we have already attained, shall make great progress in this year just as we set out to do in the last.</item>
        <item>I only want to choose your holy will.</item>
        <item>Where love and kindness (are) there God is.</item>
        <item>I live to love.</item>
        <item>I pray that God’s Will be fulfilled in you!</item>
        <item>With human bands you have drawn me to yourself. </item>
        <item>A love without the seal of the cross is suspect.</item>
        <item>My Lord and my God take everything that hinders me and everything that diminishes my great love for you.</item>
        <item>Our task as instruments consists in carefully considering God’s plans, and in giving ourselves to him without reserve…</item>
        <item>True love is never alone.</item>
        <item>Under the protection of Mary, we wish to learn how to educate ourselves.</item>
        <item>What you are determines their misfortunes and increases their happiness.</item>
        <item>I must strive for love through selflessly serving love…</item>
        <item>Father, because I am weak and small, let me always be a ` miracle of mercy. Mphc. </item>
        <item>With Father’s hand homewards!</item>
        <item>Shelter me in your richness!</item>
        <item>Free me from all inordinate self-will.</item>
        <item>Let us go forth in peace in the name of our Lord and our Lady.</item>
        <item>God’s will, therefore be still.</item>
        <item>Behold your Mother!</item>
        <item>You for me and I for you and we both for one another.</item>
        <item>The Father loves an interiorly free and happy child. Therefore I pray, – ‘Let there be the new person, who conducts himself as Christ did, free and strong, on earth …</item>
        <item>It is in the plan this way!</item>
        <item>The child may live on Father’s goodness and mercy.</item>
        <item>Seriously live up to the blank check and inscriptio…</item>
        <item>Let there be the little Mary totally given and abandoned to the Father, to his wish and will!</item>
        <item>A child lives for the moment!</item>
        <item>All that has come about from here is her work.</item>
        <item>I know that you are my Father! Mphc!</item>
        <item>I am most pleasing to the highest because I am small.</item>
        <item>Schoenstatt my world, my world shall become Schoenstatt.</item>
        <item>A servant of Mary will never perish.</item>
        <item>Nos cum prole pia benedicat Virgo Maria!</item>
        <item>With hope and joy and confident in the victory we go with Mary into the newest times!</item>
        <item>Your conversation shall be in heaven – in Father’s heart and will and in his world of values. </item>
        <item>The goal is to win the treasure in the field.</item>
        <item>Ask Him: Lord help my unbelief!</item>
        <item>Whether we meet with failure or success,we want to proclaim your love.</item>
        <item>I only want to carry out God’s plan, not my own.</item>
        <item>You know the way for me, that is enough.</item>
        <item>All for love.</item>
        <item>God loves a joyful giver.</item>
        <item>I came upon the earth to reveal the name of the Father to all.</item>
        <item>Our place is under and on the cross.</item>
        <item>It is a plan of love, a plan of wisdom, a plan of omnipotence.</item>
        <item>No one loves us more tenderly and deeply than the Father.</item>
        <item>Strive to be very kind and selfless, become all things to all people.</item>
        <item>Mother we stretch out our hands to you.</item>
        <item>I always do what pleases the Father. Inwardly everything remains unchanged.</item>
        <item>Though storm may rage and wind may howl and lightning strike again, I think as does the mariner’s child: My father is at the helm!</item>
        <item>Our hearts belong to all people, to all nations, whatever their name or their history.</item>
        <item>Do not trouble yourselves about the fulfillment of your wishes. I love those who love me.</item>
        <item>Holy Spirit, you are the soul of my soul.</item>
        <item>Remain simple, loyal and strong.</item>
        <item>The Blessed Mother is the ideal of human dignity…</item>
        <item>No one will be lost who lives the covenant in loyalty.</item>
        <item>Cor unum in Patre.</item>
        <item>I served and my reward was peace.</item>
        <item>Guide us according to that great plan of love you have designed for our Love must be the fundamental principal of our lives.</item>
        <item>To pray means: at all times to find a way to God.</item>
        <item>The light of faith tells me that whatever he wishes,permits, and ordains is good for me.</item>
        <item>I have called you by name: You are mine!</item>
        <item>Triune God, quietly speak your words of omnipotence: ‘Let there be the heavenly person on this curse-laden earth’</item>
        <item>It remains this way: Carefree because faithful! M.p.h.c.!</item>
        <item>The heavenly Father is always with us; we have no reason to be afraid.</item>
        <item>I will never forget you, never forget me! Mpcev!</item>
        <item>He is the main character, the main actor.</item>
        <item>Allow nothing and no one to disturb you – always keep but one aim in mind: My God and my all!</item>
        <item>A hero is someone who dedicates his life to a great cause.</item>
        <item>We must make this belief in Divine Providence a central part of our own life!</item>
        <item>Let this faith gladden my soul and make my love burn brightly.</item>
        <item>I remain a child!</item>
        <item>Take the picture of the Blessed Mother with you and enshrine it in your home.</item>
        <item>We must have one passion: to belong to God, to serve God, to do his work.</item>
        <item>When we consider our own strength, we lose all hope and confidence. Mother, we stretch out our hands to you and ask for your many gifts of love.</item>
        <item>If we resemble Christ in what we are and do, we may extend our hands to one another.</item>
        <item>When we see the intimate union between Christ and Mary, we have to say: the dearest word is MTA.</item>
        <item>We want to use all means to draw the world and human hearts heavenwards to the Father.</item>
        <item>Father, in the simplicity of my heart I have given you joyfully everything today!</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>